<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kseniya</title>
    <link>https://kseniya.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kseniya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kseniya.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Devcon V: Panel on Inclusion &amp; Diversity</title>
      <link>https://kseniya.io/speaking/devcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kseniya.io/speaking/devcon/</guid>
      <description>Devcon V I was on a panel about Diversity and Inclusion in the blockchain space at Devcon V in Osaka, Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ERC-1155 : Across the Multiverse</title>
      <link>https://kseniya.io/speaking/erc1155/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kseniya.io/speaking/erc1155/</guid>
      <description>ERC-1155 : Across the Multiverse I gave a talk about Ethereum tokens and token standards: Meetup Event</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAppLadies Workshop: Intro to Solidity</title>
      <link>https://kseniya.io/speaking/dapp-ladies-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kseniya.io/speaking/dapp-ladies-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Intro to Solidity Part I &amp;amp; II In this Intro to Solidity workshop, I&amp;rsquo;ll be starting with a basic overview of blockchain technology and and its history and progressing into teaching Solidity and how to write smart contracts. I&amp;rsquo;ll go over developer tools and the basic components that make up a smart contract. Part II will expand upon these concepts and participants will be coding their very own smart contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Website</title>
      <link>https://kseniya.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 21:43:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kseniya.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>I was reminiscing about my first website (the one that has been down for months).
It was a Jekyll site, which was fun to build.
I spent countless hours designing and redesigning it. Switching images, colors, fonts, header sizes. Should the headers be Sans or Sans-serif? Should I go for a minimalist look or use bright colors to make it standout? How many pictures of myself are too many pictures? I need to do a photoshoot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Teach Code Lightning Talks</title>
      <link>https://kseniya.io/speaking/why-i-love-blockchain-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:34:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kseniya.io/speaking/why-i-love-blockchain-technology/</guid>
      <description>Why I Love Blockchain Technology Learn Teach Code is a tech organization based in Los Angeles, CA. In March of 2018, they held a Two-Minute Tech Talk Contest. I gave a talk about why I love blockchain technology and placed as one of the five winners.
Slides
Content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women in Coding: Intro to HTML &amp; CSS Workshop</title>
      <link>https://kseniya.io/speaking/womenincoding-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 18:29:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kseniya.io/speaking/womenincoding-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Intermediate HTML &amp;amp; CSS This was a three hour workshop that built on top of the Introduction to HTML &amp;amp; CSS that Women in Coding was hosting. In this class, I taught students standard design practices like using a reset stylesheet, fixed navigation menus, hero images, web fonts, animations, and the basics of responsive design.
Meetup Event</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women in Coding: Intro to HTML &amp; CSS Workshop</title>
      <link>https://kseniya.io/speaking/womenincoding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 22:43:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kseniya.io/speaking/womenincoding/</guid>
      <description>Intro to HTML &amp;amp; CSS Workshop This was a two-part, 4-hour introduction to HTML &amp;amp; CSS hosted by Women in Coding. The class taught students how to structure a webpage with HTML and style if with CSS.
Meetup Event</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://kseniya.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kseniya.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Co-founder and smart contract developer at Upstate Interactive, a software consultancy headquartered in Syracuse, NY.
I wrote my first line of HTML &amp;amp; CSS in 2015. Within the next two years I quit my job, started a company, packed my life in my car and moved across the country.
I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about blockchain technology and getting more women into tech. In Syracuse, I co-founded Women in Coding to provide education resources for women in the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://kseniya.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kseniya.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email me: kseniya@upstateinteractive.io</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>